Guide to the Cornell University Reunion Miscellany, 1871-2010.
Cornell University Reunion Miscellany, 1871-2010.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University reunion miscellany, 1871-2010.
41-4-361
3.5 cubic ft.
Pamphlets, Newsletters, Newspaper articles, Photographs, Programs, Class directories, Broadsides.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Primarily programs and pamphlets relating to reunion activities of various Cornell classes.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Primarily programs and pamphlets relating to reunion activities of various Cornell classes. Also included are broadsides, programs, class directories, photographs, newsletters, correspondence, clippings, and other materials related to many classes and reunions.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.
Subjects:
Universities and colleges--Alumni and alumnae.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Reunion Miscellany
  - Class of 1871 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1872 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1873 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1874 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1875 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1877 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1878 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1880 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1881 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1882 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1884 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1885 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1886 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1887 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1888 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1889 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1890 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1891 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1892 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1893 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1894 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1895 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1896 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1899 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1900 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1901 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1902 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1903 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1904 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1906 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1907 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1908 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1909 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1910 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1911 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1912 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1913 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1914 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1915 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1916 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1917 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1918 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1919 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1920 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1921 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Class of 1922 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Class of 1923 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1924 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Class of 1925 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Class of 1926 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Class of 1927 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Class of 1928 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Class of 1929 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Class of 1930 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1931 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1932 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1933 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1934 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1935 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1936 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1937 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1942 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1945 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1953 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Reunion Guides and Miscellany
  - Cornell Reunion 1938 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Reunion 1939 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Reunion 1946 (Box 2, Folder 23a)
  - Cornell Reunion 1948 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Reunion 1949 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Reunion 1950 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Reunion 1951 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Reunion 1952 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Reunion 1953 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Reunion 1954 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Reunion 1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Reunion 1956 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Reunion 1957 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Reunion 1958 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Reunion 1959 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cornell Reunion 1960 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Reunion 1961 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Reunion 1963 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Reunion 1964 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Cornell Reunion 1965 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Cornell Reunion 1966 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cornell Reunion 1967 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Cornell Reunion 1968 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cornell Reunion 1969 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cornell Reunion 1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cornell Reunion 1974 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cornell Reunion 1975 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Cornell Reunion 1978 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Cornell Reunion 1979 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Cornell Reunion 1980 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Cornell Reunion 1981 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Cornell Reunion 1982 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Cornell Reunion 1985 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Cornell Reunion 1986 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Cornell Reunion 1987 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cornell Reunion 1988 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Cornell Reunion 1989 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Cornell Reunion 1990 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Cornell Reunion 1991 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Cornell Reunion 1992 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Cornell Reunion 1993 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Cornell Reunion 1994 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Cornell Reunion 1995 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Cornell Reunion 1996 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Cornell Reunion 1997 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Cornell Reunion 1998 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Cornell Reunion 1999 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Cornell Reunion 2000 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Cornell Reunion 2001 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Cornell Reunion 2002 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Cornell Reunion 2003 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Cornell Reunion 2004 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Cornell Reunion 2005 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Cornell Reunion 2006 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Cornell Reunion 2007 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Cornell Reunion 2008 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Cornell Reunion 2009 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Cornell Reunion 2010 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Miscellaneous Reunion Materials
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 13-15, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 13-15, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 7-9, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 12-13, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 12-13, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Club of NY Questionnaires & Reports, May 23 - Dec. 20, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 16-18, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 16-18, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Mailings to Alumni Leaders, June 12, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Magazines and Newsletters from Various Universities (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Magazines and Newsletters from Various Universities (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Annual Class Officers Meeting, Jan. 9, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "Cornell Report," "Letter from Cornell," "Cornell Council Reports," 1956-1964 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "Cornell Report," "Letter from Cornell," "Cornell Council Reports," 1956-1964 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fraternity Newsletters, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fraternity Newsletters, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 17-19, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Reunion Chairman's Manual, June 17-19, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Reunion Memorial Services (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reunion Scrapbook, including 1978-1991 (Box 4)